(Yuseong Technical High School Bulletin Board)
(1 year ago)
Hey.
Move aside, you punks.
Fucking hell.
(School Disciplinary Committee Meeting Notice)
(Location: Yuseong Tech Academic Affairs Conference Room. Subjects: Bang Sang-in, Choo Jae-hwang, Ma Min-hwan, Pi Han-wool)
Damn it. So embarrassing. Crap.
This is that woman Jung-hwa's doing, isn't it?
Fuck. Is she senile? That bitch.
(Meeting Initiator: Teacher Oh Jung-hwa)
Han-wool.
I heard you're getting sent to the disciplinary committee?
Graduating cleanly...
Is it that hard?
I will definitely take care of it.
Humans are animals that act entirely for their own benefit.
Are you scared?
I've always thought...
No human is born a bad guy.
So,
You can change too.
You,
A high schooler trying to look tough with dead eyes like yours...
Do you think I haven't dealt with that before?
Teacher.
People don't change easily.
Pi Han-wool.
That woman too...
She's just using me under the guise of being a 'righteous teacher.'
Ugh, no...
Ah... What are you doing?
Mom.
In an alley in Dong-gu, Ancheon,
A woman in her 40s who died from a random stabbing...
Has been identified as a teacher at Y High School.
(Arrest Warrant Requested for Teenage Suspect in Ancheon Female Teacher Random Murder)
The suspect is a Mr. Song, over 15 years old.
It is reported that he turned himself in to the police after the crime.
During the police investigation,
As it was determined that Mr. Song posed a flight risk,
An arrest warrant has been requested.
The Disciplinary Committee...
Will probably wrap up as if this never happened, Han-wool.
Come on, everyone check your phones.
(The only way to become a prospective family member of the Yeonbaek Gang!
Yuseong Tech Ranking App OPEN. Download App)
The guys who download the app and prove their strength...
Will become prospective family members of the Yeonbaek Gang.
(1st Year: 1st Place, 2nd Place, 3rd Place, 4th Place, 5th Place)
Start.
I will make this school...
Return to normal.
I don't care who they are.
What the...
(School Disciplinary Committee Meeting Notice)
(Present)
What should we do?
Looks like you're getting dragged to the disciplinary committee.
Just sit tight and wait to die.
(3rd Period: English Domain, Odd Type)
(Korean Domain, 3rd Period: English Domain, Odd Type,
Math Domain)
(Those who want to study, gather around!)
(Hwang Min-hyun)
(Han Ji-eun)
(Cha Woo-min)
(Lee Jong-hyun)
(Shin Soo-hyun)
(Yoon Sang-jung, Gong Do-yoo)
"Study Group"
(Even in hell, I will create an opportunity)
-This? -Did you use it yourself?
The atmosphere at school seems a bit different lately.
Right? I felt it too.
The ranking update hasn't moved at all today either.
This is the first time since the app was created, right?
Did the people at Yuseong Tech quit fighting?
Wow, is this for real?
It's all thanks to Teacher Han-kyung.
And...
Also thanks to Yoon Ga-min.
What are you doing?
Please do not convene the disciplinary committee.
What?
Didn't I tell you before?
An equivalent price.
Don't trust these things too much.
Didn't you say that before?
That I resemble your late mother.
What did you mean by that?
That question had always been on my mind.
I found this out while investigating that case.
The late Teacher Oh Jung-hwa's son attends Yuseong Tech.
I'm sorry.
I should have known sooner and taken better care of you.
But Gun-yeop.
Teacher Oh Jung-hwa's case...
What does it have to do with Pi Han-wool's disciplinary committee?
Because the guy who killed my mom...
Is Pi Han-wool.
Wasn't the culprit in the teacher's case caught?
Did you naively believe that?
He's just a fall guy serving time for the Yeonbaek Gang.
Doesn't Teacher also know what kind of guy Pi Han-wool is?
If he's done it once, could he not do it again?
-Gun-yeop. -I'll just...
Stop it here. Please.
I don't know if it's because of that substitute teacher...
But she's only been digging into Han-wool's business lately.
She's prepared a ton of documents to submit to the disciplinary committee.
I was going to stop her no matter what...
Hey, you.
Have you always been this unreasonable?
Why would you sign something like this?
Why drag me into this too?
The Ministry of Education's inspection is already scheduled.
I couldn't help it, Vice Principal.
There's no way now...
To stop Pi Han-wool's disciplinary committee from convening.
If not handled well,
Han-wool might not be able to escape expulsion.
Han-wool.
I have something to say to the Chairman.
If you're done talking, please leave.
What?
Understood.
Th... then I'll contact you again.
You should just go study abroad...
The disciplinary committee won't be held.
Please don't worry, I can handle it.
(The 'Thug' High Schoolers Who Broke Out into a Fight While Stealing in the Middle of the Night)
Last night, a mass brawl broke out in a building in Ancheon.
It caused a huge stir on social media.
According to informants,
These people are first-year students at a technical high school in Ancheon.
(The 'Thug' High Schoolers Who Broke Out into a Fight While Stealing in the Middle of the Night)
To hide their identities, they secretly wore other schools' uniforms...
And broke into a store attempting to steal goods.
(Surprise Raid on Thug Headquarters.
Gangster Training Camp 'Yuseong Tech' Pilgrimage)
Hello, viewers.
I am now at this infamous gangster training school...
In front of Yuseong Tech.
The true identities of the thugs on the news yesterday are circulating online...
They are none other than Yuseong Tech's Study Group.
Let's uncover the truth.
What the...
Grew up in Hope Orphanage.
Along with her twin brother, Lee Hyun-woo.
-Damn it. -They've been notorious delinquents since they were young.
Oh my god, why are you doing this? Please move.
Hey, Choi Hee-won.
People say you used to be a loser loner...
Then met the delinquent Lee Ji-woo and became her lackey.
-Where did these flies come from?
-Put the camera away!
You guys are Yuseong Tech students, right?
I heard there's a violent club in the school, is it true?
What?
-No... -Wait, red hair.
-Red hair! -Yeah!
-Student, could it be... -Right, red hair.
-Student... -Right.
-Student... -Hold on...
Hey, Lee Ji-woo.
Run...
It's the red hair!
Um, Vice Principal.
You said you're sending Ga-min to the disciplinary committee.
What does that mean?
Haven't you been watching the news?
There must be some misunderstanding.
I can guarantee that my students are not thugs.
The school is completely surrounded by reporters right now.
Do you know how hard I had to work to block them off?
I will first figure out what happened...
Stop with the hindsight.
You caused this, so please take responsibility.
Whether it's sending Yoon Ga-min and those kids to the disciplinary committee...
And expelling them all.
Or canceling Pi Han-wool's disciplinary committee.
What?
I think the first step should be disbanding the study group.
Vice Principal.
And you get ready to write your resignation letter.
Once the study group is abolished...
Your contract also ends. This condition...
You still remember it, right?
You all must have been terrified.
I'm sorry, Teacher.
It's all because of me...
I already heard from Detective Na Tae-man.
You did that to save Kim Soon-chul from our school.
Of course,
It was wrong for you to hide it from me and do something so dangerous.
But,
Your intentions weren't wrong.
However,
Never step forward and do dangerous things again.
Promise me.
-Okay. -Okay.
Whether it's the news or the disciplinary committee...
I will find a way to turn the situation around.
That is what I am supposed to do.
So,
Please trust me and wait a little bit.
No matter who tries to start trouble, absolutely do not get involved.
Especially...
Ga-min.
I know you feel wronged.
But please bear with it for a moment.
I'm begging you.
Okay.
What about Teacher Han-kyung?
Exactly.
We are one thing...
But even the teacher is about to be fired by the school.
That absolutely cannot happen.
Damn it. We have to deal with that bastard rotten egg.
This is all his doing.
What?
Shit, what's going on?
What's wrong?
The ranking app is now...
-What's going on? -What's going on?
Bastards.
Special Announcement.
Those who raise their ranking within 1 hour...
Can get a prize of 1 million won.
Our Yuseong Tech is really full of energy.
Crazy bastards.
Damn it.
Try hitting me.
I told you that guy Kim Se-hyun is a coward.
You might win if you throw the first punch.
Kim Se-hyun, you bastard.
I have to earn that 1 million won. Hit me!
Fuck.
Damn it.
Forget it.
I'm fine, you go in.
Let's go in together.
If...
No matter how hard we try, nothing changes, what do we do?
What?
Even if we study hard and get into college...
What if society is just like Yuseong Tech?
It won't be like that.
I always thought things could change.
But...
Having a dream...
Having a dream is just too hard.
(Dad)
Hello?
You're here.
Your show is really good.
Give me an autograph.
That's all fake news.
The truth will be revealed someday.
An appropriate story, plus a little bit of truth...
Becomes the truth in this world.
People will bite hard, but the hype will soon fade.
After that, regardless of the truth...
You guys will just be considered a violent gang.
Yoon Ga-min.
Is it worth going this far for these classmates?
No matter what you do...
Yuseong Tech won't change.
I can give them what they want.
Whether it's money or connections.
But what can you give them?
Dreams?
Hope?
Do those trash living day-by-day
really want these things?
Get this straight.
Here, I am the reality.
Tell Lee Han-kyung to cancel the disciplinary committee.
Then we'll let you graduate.
Move...
(Student Council)
What's going on?
What the hell are you guys doing?
Ah, I forgot to mention.
It seems you don't need a club room anymore.
I heard that before the disciplinary committee is held...
Your club's status has been revoked.
Hey, flip it.
You made a promise with Teacher Han-kyung.
Ga-min.
I know you feel wronged.
But please bear with it.
I'm begging you.
(Even in hell, I will create an opportunity)
Enough.
What's your problem, punk?
You guys only spout nonsense when you open your mouths.
Of course you call a delinquent like that a filthy thug.
Am I supposed to call him 'teacher'?
Did you see it with your own eyes?
Have you ever seen my son acting like a thug, you bastard?!
Damn it.
Wow, you're still defending a guy like that as your son.
What did you say, you bastard?!
Come here!
Get over here, you punk!
You bastard...
Are you really a thug?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you really some kind of delinquent?
You little punk...
You kept making a fuss about finishing high school...
Was it just to do things like that?!
Even if you're a parasite who can't support yourself at this age...
You still shouldn't be a thug!
I'll go to the construction site.
What did you say?
I said I'll drop out.
And start making money.
Oh my god.
Hey, look at them.
Is that them?
Hey, Lee Ji-woo.
Her brother is also a delinquent who stabbed a teacher.
Oh my, it seems your family background really determines your character.
They're such a dramatic sibling pair.
Lee Hyun-woo is in juvie now.
They really do have different blood.
Did their parents go to jail and abandon them?
Unbelievable.
Hey.
No...
What.
They didn't say anything wrong.
But insulting their parents is crossing the line, right?
Those bitches don't know anything at all.
Choi Hee-won, you've really become a delinquent.
Swearing so easily.
I'm not a delinquent.
I'm your lackey.
My parents both work at KEPCO.
We live in a luxury apartment, super fucking rich.
So I survive by paying tribute to you.
Your parents' company got exposed. What are you going to do?
It doesn't matter.
They don't really care about me anyway.
Choi Hee-won.
Mom.
Dad.
You... Didn't I tell you to come straight home after school?
-Come here quickly. -What are you staring at?
Bye.
Seriously, you really don't listen.
(Yuseong Tech Study Group)
Are you guys okay?
I'm a bit pissed off today.
Stop leaving me on read.
Are we really going to be finished?
I... actually started finding studying a bit fun lately.
Ah, fuck. Are you all dead?
Why is no one replying?
(I'm fine)
(At least we...)
(Kim Se-hyun has left the group. Invite to group)
No matter how hard we try, nothing changes, what do we do?
Having a dream...
Having a dream is just too hard.
I can give them what they want.
Whether it's money or connections.
But what can you give them?
Let's eat.
What's wrong?
Are things not going well?
The study group...
Is probably going to disband.
We just...
Wanted to study.
Ga-min.
Do you know why I agreed to let you stay at Yuseong Tech?
Because you looked...
Happier than ever.
(Even in hell, I will create an opportunity)
-Nice! -What is that?
-How did you come up with a phrase like that? -Nice!
(Studying)
Here, mark this question with two stars.
You're exactly like Teacher Han-kyung.
Minerals.
And this is Omega 3.
One, two, three.
And this.
It contains egg yolk lecithin.
-Really? -Yeah.
I heard these are all good for brain cells.
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
If Yoon Ga-min eats all of this,
won't his body never rot even after he dies?
Hey, Yoon Ga-min.
Look at his cheeks.
-You look like a dummy. -What are you thinking about?
Why are your cheeks so red?
Your cheeks are the same color as Joon's hair right now.
Why is your face so red?
Try doing this...
(Even in hell, I will create an opportunity)
(Investigation Data for Student Pi Han-wool's Disciplinary Committee)
Isn't student Kim Soon-chul a witness?
Because he is the party involved and also a student at Yuseong Tech,
The credibility of his testimony will decrease.
Then...
Do my students just have to take the fall?
I'm sorry to say this,
But I have to ask you to just wait and see for now.
Before Yoon Ga-min gets expelled because of your persistence in holding the disciplinary committee...
You should just give up.
Head of Academic Affairs.
It can't be helped.
This is the current reality of the school.
I understand your good intentions.
Let's stop here.
(Investigation Data for Student Pi Han-wool's Disciplinary Committee)
(Documents for Student Pi Han-wool's Disciplinary Committee)
(Are you sure you want to delete?
Documents for Student Pi Han-wool's Disciplinary Committee)
(Yes)
(Even in hell, I will create an opportunity)
You must memorize the cubic multiplication formulas.
(a plus b) cubed...
Equals a cubed plus 3 a squared b...
Plus 3 a b squared plus b cubed.
Come on, repeat it three times.
(a plus b) cubed...
Equals a cubed plus b cubed...
Next is (a minus b) cubed.
a minus...
Teacher.
Let's clean up.
What the...
Why are you here?
So what you're saying is...
You'll be taking Mr. Kim's place for work from now on?
Yes.
Even though I can't fully handle my dad's job yet...
I'm willing to do anything.
And who are you?
I'm a buy-one-get-one-free freebie.
You really...
Go back.
I'll only leave when you leave.
I'm going to study with you and go to college.
Damn it.
What? Bricks? Put the bricks over there.
Okay.
-Are you okay? -Didn't I tell you to go back?
If we work together, we can finish sooner.
Hey, there's no fixed individual workload here.
How can we finish sooner?
I'm going to study with you and go to college.
You really...
Hey, Yoon Ga-min.
Please, just go back.
I don't want to study.
I'm not going to college, you psycho.
What?
What are you...
I will definitely study with you.
And go to college together.
Seriously...
-Did you just smile? -Yeah. Let's go.
You said go together? Really?
Yes, you college-repeating parrot.
Wait a minute.
Let's go.
Seriously.
Huh, what's going on?
Oh my.
I wondered where you ran off to.
So you did come. But where are you going?
Isn't work not over yet?
Um, Mister...
Dad.
Thank you.
For raising me all this time.
I only realized after coming here...
How hard you work.
But...
I really want to study.
Please just wait for me for three years.
I will really work my ass off.
I will definitely become successful.
I absolutely...
Will not make you regret it, Dad.
Mister, please wait and see.
Because Se-hyun...
Will become the owner of a building like this in the future.
Let's go.
Hello.
I am...
(Yuseong Technical High School First Year Midterm Exams)
Ranked first in our entire school.
Ah, that's right.
He's number one in the whole school.
Hee-won's grades also improved because we studied together in the study group.
The rumors about us being thugs are really all misunderstandings.
Um...
Actually, because we were so worried...
We were planning to transfer Hee-won...
No.
Yuseong Tech, you see...
Many people use the special admission tracks for vocational high schools...
To get into universities in Seoul.
You didn't know that, right?
-Into universities in Seoul? -Yes.
Universities in Seoul.
Just leave it to me.
As Hee-won's study partner, I will keep a close eye on her.
And successfully get her into a school in Seoul.
But...
What is that?
I learned that it's impolite to visit a friend's house empty-handed.
But why blueberries of all things?
Because blueberries are a superfood that activates the brain.
The brain?
Yes.
You guys are so thoughtful.
I really hope when I get to college, I'll have friends to go to departmental mixers with.
A loner like me probably won't make any friends even in college.
Then I definitely won't be able to go to departmental mixers either.
What a shame.
Oh my.
How fun would it be if we both got boyfriends and went out together?
Besides, our types are different.
You look at faces, I look at bodies.
What right do I have to go to college and get a boyfriend?
Why would you say that?
What's wrong with you?
Alright.
Let's just say I barely get into college like you said, and go to a departmental mixer.
Then what should I say when I introduce myself?
Say that I'm a poor girl from an orphanage?
And I have a twin brother, but he's currently in jail?
And I'm busy to death trying to send him food?
Want to find some time to go visit him in prison with me?
You want me to say that?
It's not wrong, though.
But don't you think some guys might think like this?
"Despite the difficult situation of coming from an orphanage..."
"Even though her brother is locked up..."
"She worked so hard at part-time jobs and got into college."
"And takes such good care of her brother too."
"She's a really cool and amazing girl."
If you marry a guy like that...
Then the bouquet...
I'll catch it.
(Yuseong Tech Study Group 5)
(Yoon Ga-min invited Kim Se-hyun)
What the, where did you run off to, Kim Se-hyun?
I went to cool off a bit.
You absolutely have to hold the disciplinary committee, don't you?
Yes.
Once the handover is complete and the disciplinary committee is over...
I will leave.
Does it not matter even if those kids in the study group get hurt?
If you were a real teacher, you should protect the students.
My students aren't just the ones in the study group.
I have already promised to protect all the students hurt by Pi Han-wool.
For that, I still believe that Yuseong Tech needs to change.
Teacher Lee Han-kyung.
If...
The kids in the study group really did something wrong,
Then I will have them fairly accept their punishment and reflect on themselves.
But...
I won't stand by and let them be falsely accused.
"Study Group"
© 2025 Tving & Studio Dragon All Rights Reserved